EPISODE 2: THE DESTINED ONE
Hello, Miss Witch.
So, hey, what's your name?
Yeah, yeah. I mean you.
It's the boy from your drawing.
Not only was it very rare for someone to
approach the witch without hostility,
but she was also consumed by regret and
guilt for what she'd done days before.
My name is Henri.
Say, would your name happen to be Luna?
Whoa, hitting on a black witch?
No way.
Henri's sure got some stones.
A hero among womanizers.
We've met somewhere before...
haven't we?
Seriously?
Well, dang.
Even the way he got
rejected is inconceivable.
Moo! Luna, wait for me!
Oh. There she is.
Mister Bull, your friend came back for you.
Straight out of a mushroom, of all things!
Moo! Luna, you dummy, dummy!
You abandoned me!
I'm sorry.
- Moo!
- Are you all right?
Mister Bull told me all about how shy you are.
Pet me more than that!
I didn't mean to surprise you. I'm sorry.
A-And I'm sorry for running away like that.
U-Um... and for the other stuff I did to you.
I apologize.
I knew it! It really wasn't my imagination!
We really have met somewhere before.
We danced in a moonlit sky, didn't we?
You have memories from the drawing!
I couldn't forget the way you looked that night.
Still, on that night, why...
Whoa!
Please don't try to touch me.
Stay away from me. Please.
That wasn't your real body that night.
That's why I was able to touch you then.
But the truth is, my body is full of poisons
that would be very dangerous to you.
I'm sorry for drawing a picture
of you without permission!
Incredible! I've heard the rumors about you.
About the Champignon Witch. Mushrooms really
do sprout from everything you touch!
What a surprise! You and the mushrooms
are so much cuter than I imagined!
I could tell when we met before, but
you aren't like the rumors say at all.
Do you only make poison mushrooms grow,
though? Is it okay if I touch this one?
It's so cute.
Whoa!
What just happened?
I'm sorry.
No need to apologize.
You just have a really interesting way
of showing embarrassment, Luna.
Seriously, there's never a dull moment with you.
Henri... You're one to talk, man.
He's turning into one of those studs
who has tragically bad taste in women.
Oh, because of your poison breath?
That amorous personality of his
will get him into trouble.
Yeah, but his puppy dog-like
charm is what hooks people.
But is this really okay? I hear his family's
all devoted white witch fundamentalists.
Loyal to the crown types.
Huh.
Sure, but Henri isn't like that.
Okay, but still, if one of his relatives
saw this, there'd be hell to pay.
Yeah, he'd probably get chewed out for it.
Henri would, sure. But that black witch?
She'll end up on the witch
hunt list at this rate.
Yeah.
I'm not a fan of that kind of stuff.
That idiot!
What the hell does she think she's doing?
No need to keep apologizing for the drawing.
I'm really flattered that you liked
my face that much, actually.
I think when my soul passed
through the drawing to see you,
it wasn't only because of your powers.
Huh?
I'm nowhere near the level of a witch or wizard,
but I guess because of my background, I do
have a kind of knack for things like that.
The white witches in my family
are all really stuck up and mean.
I could always tell they looked down on me,
so I never thought too highly of them.
But you aren't like that at
all, Luna! It's so strange.
When I'm with you,
even with all your poisons,
my heart, even the air around me
feels like it's been purified.
Nobody else does that for me.
It's like you and your mushrooms wash
away everything rotten around me.
Is that part of your magic, too?
She's over there!
Luna?
What's wrong, Lu—
You.
What happened to the black
witch that was just here?
Where did she go?
- Impossible!
- What was that?
Lu—
Wait! Will I see you again?
I really want to! If you feel the same way,
then draw another picture of me!
And I'll come see you! I'll be waiting!
Hey. Get the hell up already.
Claude?
What's all the commotion, guys?
What the hell was that about?
Making a move on someone under the white
witches' protection, and in broad daylight?
If the military police had captured you,
you wouldn't have gotten off easy.
Have you completely forgotten who you are?
You failure of a witch!
Cool it.
You don't just barge into someone else's
home and start ranting. Stop it.
At least explain what's going on.
So in other words, Miss Witch is
finally opening her eyes to romance?
Romance, my ass.
Huh. That's great, Miss Witch.
Maybe those romance novels had an effect?
- Good for you!
- Hmph! How lame.
Don't get jealous, now.
Nobody's jealous!
This crow boy was someone who
always watched over Luna.
He was the familiar of a great
and respected wizard.
For some reason, he was always
very controlling with Luna,
but he would also help her whenever needed.
He was a difficult, complicated person.
Look. You're not seeing that guy again. Ever.
I don't have a clue what you're planning,
but if you ever try to mess around with
him again, I'll go straight to my master.
Because if something goes wrong, it's not
gonna end with just you getting purged.
It's gonna involve all of us
black witches and wizards.
You got that?
Mm-hmm.
- So this like this, and...
- This is hard to draw.
Luna, did you see anything nice today?
Draw a picture of the prettiest
thing you saw in town today!
I hope it's food. Something
red and tasty looking.
I want to see you again.
When I'm with you, my heart
feels like it's been purified.
I'll be waiting.
Luna?
Her hand started moving on its own,
and before she knew it, a drawing
spilled out onto the page.
It's the boy from before!
She'd merely wished to retrace the words
he'd said, the way he'd looked...
The Henri from the drawing couldn't speak.
Thank you for drawing my picture again.
I wanted to see you so badly, Luna.
But don't I look a little messier than before?
I didn't intend to see you again.
I thought that if I drew you,
it would cause trouble for the real you again.
But if I drew you poorly, maybe
you wouldn't appear anyway.
At least, that's what I told myself.
Even if it was an inanimate picture,
I just had to see you again.
Even though I know I shouldn't have. I'm sorry.
But seeing you now still
makes me so happy. I'm sorry.
Don't cry, Luna.
Your tears are beautiful,
but I'd rather see you smiling.
When I'm like this, I can't
even wipe away your tears.
It's so frustrating.
Luna, when we danced in the moonlight,
you had tears in your eyes then, too.
And again when we were talking in town.
Did I do something wrong?
Something that upset you?
No.
Those were tears of joy. No one had ever
touched me with such kindness before,
and it made me so happy. I felt such joy.
I was overcome with it,
but also sadness at the thought
of that moment ending.
I'd never known such joy before in my life.
I'm scared even now. How could such
ultimate joy also be so terrifying?
If I want more, I fear it may come at
the cost of someone else...
That it would destroy your joy in exchange.
Luna, everything will be all right.
I know that you will continue to
find joy in life. I promise it.
I want you to come with me, to find
what awaits beyond ultimate joy.
To capture a joy that won't fade so easily.
So let's find a way to
spend more time together.
I'm willing to do absolutely
anything for you, Luna.
I want to be with you forever.
So keep drawing me, Luna. Now and forever.
I'll be fine! You don't need to worry
about me. Do you understand, Luna?
Because now, the only thing in this world
that scares me is the thought of losing you.
Did you hear about Henri?
He's been bedridden for a while now.
But the doctors can't find anything wrong.
They don't know why he's getting so gaunt.
Didn't he start acting strangely
after meeting that black witch?
Henri's family said they're going to
appeal to the white witches for help.
Tch.
Luna.
Aren't you gonna draw Henri today? I made
a promise to go shoot beans with him.
I'm going to take a break
from drawing for a while.
Why?
He's seemed kind of exhausted recently.
His lines have been looking really weak.
Don't you want to see him, Luna?
But his lines looked so weak...
So that's what's going on?
Why you...
I told you to stay away
from him, stupid witch!
Scary crow!
I'm bigger than you, so watch it!
Hey. Go see what you've
done with your own eyes.
You get it now? Even with a "knack"
for magic, he's still just a human.
You didn't once think about
the toll it takes on him.
Henri...
When a witch with your kind of
power pulls a stunt like this,
it's just like the humans and white witches
say. It's all a black witch's seduction.
Henri...
You need to put an end to this, now.
Huh?
You're Luna's mushrooms, right?
You came all the way to see me?
I'm so glad.
Along with the poison,
Luna drew from Henri's heart
a mushroom that had grown out of
his feelings for and memories of her.
More beautiful and delicate than
any mushroom she'd grown before,
it was almost like a flower.
The fact that his feelings for her
had blossomed in his heart
into something so beautiful
gave the witch great joy.
Luna, everything will be all right.
I want you to come with me, to find
what awaits beyond ultimate joy.
Henri left her with an unfading joy
that would last for the rest of her life,
no matter what happened.
The witch etched that night onto her heart.
Henri...
Thank you.
Hey! Henri!
You look good as new! You sure
had us worried for a while, man.
Sorry.
So what the heck was that
mystery disease, anyway?
People were saying it was the black
witch's curse. Is that true?
Black witch? What are you talking about?
Man... you're turning into a real dirtbag.
Seriously, what do you mean?
I'm okay.
And the days went by.
The march of the black witch
hunt grew louder and louder,
while the witch herself made
fewer and fewer trips to town.
Look, look!
Merino, see Luna's feet? They
even grow mushrooms underwater!
That's when it happened.
Luna, look!
This is bad.
That was when the witch Luna and I first met.
TRANSLATION: MICHAEL ARNOLD
SUBTITLE TIMING: ANDY ELLIS
EDITING: ELISABETH CRIST
QUALITY CHECK: GABRIELLA ALABANZA
TRANSLATION CHECK: MICHELLE TYMON
NEXT TIME: THE CURSED YOUNGLING